// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions_master = [
    {    
    question: "The cyclist ___ won the race trained hard.",
    answer: "who",
    options: [
      "that",
      "which",
      "when",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "The pants ___ I bought yesterday are already stained.",
    answer: "that",
    options: [
      "who",
      "which",
      "when",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "The four team leaders, ___  the committee selects, will be at tomorrow’s meeting.",
    answer: "whoever",
    options: [
      "who",
      "which",
      "when",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "Spaghetti, ___ we eat at least twice a week, is one of my family’s favorite meals.",
    answer: "which",
    options: [
      "who",
      "whoever",
      "when",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "Where did you buy the dress ___ you wore last week?",
    answer: "that",
    options: [
      "who",
      "whoever",
      "when",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "The book, ___ it was finally returned, was torn and stained.",
    answer: "when",
    options: [
      "who",
      "whoever",
      "that",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "The store on the corner, ___ we usually buy all of our art supplies, burned to the ground.",
    answer: "where",
    options: [
      "who",
      "whoever",
      "that",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "The festival, ___ lasted all day, ended with a banquet.",
    answer: "which",
    options: [
      "who",
      "whoever",
      "that",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "I am looking for someone ___ can watch my dog while I go on vacation.",
    answer: "who",
    options: [
      "which",
      "whoever",
      "that",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "The police needed details ___ could help identify the robber.",
    answer: "that",
    options: [
      "which",
      "whoever",
      "who",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "I’d like to take you to a café ___ serves excellent coffee.",
    answer: "which",
    options: [
      "that",
      "whoever",
      "who",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "The clubhouse, in ___ the dance was held, housed about 200 people.",
    answer: "which",
    options: [
      "that",
      "whoever",
      "who",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "You can choose one person, ___ you like, to share the cruise with you.",
    answer: "whomever",
    options: [
      "that",
      "which",
      "who",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "I saw the shoes ___ you bought last week on sale for less this week.",
    answer: "that",
    options: [
      "whomever",
      "which",
      "who",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "The winners, ___ known, will receive money and other prizes.",
    answer: "when",
    options: [
      "whomever",
      "which",
      "who",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "The baby, ___ nap had been interrupted, wailed loudly.",
    answer: "whose",
    options: [
      "whomever",
      "which",
      "who",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "___ cannot be cured must be endured.",
    answer: "what",
    options: [
      "whomever",
      "which",
      "whatever",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "She found ___ she was searching for.",
    answer: "what",
    options: [
      "whomever",
      "which",
      "whatever",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "___ I have decided,I have decided.",
    answer: "what",
    options: [
      "whomever",
      "which",
      "whatever",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "I will do ___ I want to do.",
    answer: "what",
    options: [
      "whomever",
      "which",
      "whatever",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "___ is done cannot be undone.",
    answer: "what",
    options: [
      "whomever",
      "whatever",
      "who",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "I wouln'd hear ___ she whispered.",
    answer: "what",
    options: [
      "that",
      "whatever",
      "who",
    ]
  },{    
    question: "___ he does,he does well.",
    answer: "whatever",
    options: [
      "what",
      "which",
      "who",
    ]
  },
];






